import questionImage from "../assets/question-bucket-3.svg";
export const questions = {
    bucket_name: "Renewable energy",
    image: questionImage,
    questions: [{
        question: "Which of the following is a NOT type of renewable energy?",
        options: ["Solar power",	"Hydropwer",	"Natural gas", "Geothermal energy"],
        answer: "Natural gas",
        followup_text: "Natural gas is not a type of renewable energy. It is a fossil fuel found underground, similar to petroleum.",
        source: "https://www.perchenergy.com/blog/energy/natural-gas-explained-nonrenewable#"
    },
    {
        question: "Using direct sunlight for energy was discovered by...",
        options: ["Elon Musk in 1984",	"Robert Oppenheimer in 1926",	"Edmond Becquerel in 1839"],
        answer: "Edmond Becquerel in 1839",
        followup_text: "Edmond Becquerel discovered the photovoltaic effect in 1839. It explained how electricity can be produced from sunlight.",
        source: "https://solenergy.com.ph/solar-panel-philippines-edmond-becquerel"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Solar energy can be stored in salt",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Concentrated sunlight can be used to melt salt. This forms molten salt, which is used to generate steam and electricity.",
        source: "https://www.yara.com/industrial-nitrogen/solar-power-molten-salt"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Hydrogen is a clean fuel that produces only water as a byproduct.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "As a fuel source, hydrogen produces only water as a byproduct.",
        source: "https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-explainers/what-is-hydrogen-energy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is geothermal energy?",
        options: ["Heat energy coming from within the Earth",	"Heat energy coming from the sun",	"Heat energy coming from waves hitting the shore"],
        answer: "Heat energy coming from within the Earth",
        followup_text: "Geothermal energy is a type of renewable energy taken from the Earthâ€™s core.",
        source: "https://www.twi-global.com/technical-knowledge/faqs/geothermal-energy"
    },
    {
        question: "Solar panels have been placed...",
        options: ["On the rooftops of buildings",	"On the surface of the sea",	"In space",	"All of the above"],
        answer: "All of the above",
        followup_text: "To catch the sunlight, solar panels have been placed on rooftops, on the surface of the sea and in space.",
        source: "https://www.straitstimes.com/multimedia/graphics/2022/05/singapore-solar-power-panels/index.html?shell"
    },
    {
        question: "Do solar panels work in moonlight?",
        options: ["Yes, solar panels are capable of converting moonlight into energy",	"No, moonlight is too weak be converted into energy"],
        answer: "Yes, solar panels are capable of converting moonlight into energy",
        followup_text: "Solar panels can work with moonlight, but the amount of energy generated is much lower compared to sunlight.",
        source: "https://ciir.in/effective-electricity-generation-from-moon-light-solar-panels/#:~:text=Given%20that%20moonlight%20is%20just,no%20clouds%20in%20the%20sky."
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Southeast Asia countries are burning trash to produce electricity.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Southeast Asia countries are building waste-to-energy plants to generate electricity from the heat produced during incineration.",
        source: "https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Energy/Southeast-Asia-looks-to-its-growing-piles-of-trash-as-new-energy-source"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an example of geothermal energy?",
        options: ["Volcanoes",	"Geysers",	"Hot springs",	"All of the above"],
        answer: "All of the above",
        followup_text: "Volcanoes, geysers and hot springs are natural displays of geothermal energy, which is a form of renewable energy.",
        source: "https://www.enelgreenpower.com/learning-hub/renewable-energies/geothermal-energy/natural-displays-of-geothermal-energy"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: The brakes on electric cars can be used to charge its batteries.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Known as regenerative braking, the brakes on electric cars is used to charge its batteries.",
        source: "https://www.autoexpress.co.uk/tips-advice/353643/regenerative-braking-what-it-and-how-does-it-work"
    }]
}















